THAISE RUBBO



ABOUT ME

I am a detail-oriented, insightful, and self-starter professional. I am highly motivated by complex challenges and my peers see me as a solution-oriented and resourceful problem-solver. I've been leading high-performing teams for over 7 years, bringing a creative and future-friendly mindset to my projects and teammates, always aiming to become and develop better leaders.

EXPERIENCE

MAISETC

Solution Architect

2020 - Current

Designed complex interactions between enterprise processes and technology solutions, focusing on meeting specific business needs on a tactical and operatonal level;

Helped project teams recognize and mitigate risks, improving business processes to maximize overall performance and eliminate unnecessary complexities;

Refined project status reports and data analysis processes to develop recommended operational improvements, lowering costs and improving customer service;

Direct, review and optimize operations budget, performance indicators, project scopes, market research, goals and targets;

Worked directly with business representatives and with key clients to ensure relationships were maintained and developed;

MBULLS

2019 - 2020

Project Executive

Directed multiple projects scopes through agile methodologies, directly supporting project leaders (design, engineering, marketing, sales) and their associates from ideation through implementation and launch;

Implemented processes, management standards, KPIs, and OKRs, ensuring governance and compliance to all projects;

Acted as a bridge between technical and business audiences during solution planning, development and deployment.

Responsible for research and development of new products (R&D);

Refined our customer experience program to our Stakeholders (CX Journeys & NPS);

Started a leadership empowerment program, to manage expectations, ensuring appropriate organizational structures, principles, tools and responsibilities;

Conducted feasibility studies and brainstorming sessions to develop potential solutions for our business needs and challenges.

Designed mock-ups, sketches, and documented ideas to ensure effective communication between the development, design, and customer service teams;

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Proficient in agile methodologies, software architecture, UI, UX, CX, design tools, coding tools, prototyping tools, and front-end development; Strong learning capabilities, result-orientation, and diligent personality; Excellent creative direction and project management knowledge; Significant adaptability, analytical capacity, and proactivity; Proven experience in sales, negotiation, and stakeholder management;

LANGUAGES

English	
Portuguese	
Spanish	

THAISE RUBBO



EDUCATION

EACH USP Univeristy of São Paulo

2019 - 2019

Singularity Univeristy

2018 - 2018

ECA USP Univeristy of São Paulo

2017 - on hold

EEFE USP Univeristy of São Paulo

2012 - 2016

Web Development, Certificate

Areas of study:

Design Patterns, UI, UX, HTML, HTML 5, CSS, CSS 3, JavaScript, React, ReactJS, MySQL, Firebase, PHP, Laravel, R, NodeJS;

Incubator Program, Certificate

Areas of study:

Exponential Technologies, Futurism, Entrepreneurship, Social Entrepreneurship, Governance, Future of Work, Abundance & Prosperity, Smart & Connected Cities, Al, Robotics, Space, STEM;

Public Relations, Master Certificate

Areas of study:

Public Relations, Advertising, Crisis management, Organizational Communication, Marketing, Branding, Strategic Management, Ethics, Entrepreneurship;

Sport, Bachelor of Applied Science (B.A.Sc.)

Areas of study:

Sport Applied Sciences: Anatomy, Biochemistry, Biomechanics, Physiology, Statistics; Sport Management: Business, Governance, Marketing, Events, Economics, Sociology, Politics;

REFERENCES